Qi Luo

Full Stack Engineer

Self-motivator good at finding reliable solutions for system issues. Experienced in working as a full stack developer and leading an offshore team. Providing reliable skills in both development and technical communication. Fluent in English&Japanese and accustomed to working with cross-cultural teams.



Work History

2018-04 -Current

Full Stack Engineer

D.A.Consortium Inc., Tokyo

- Created detailed specifications and developed features that satisfied clients expectations on an Ads delivering configuration system and a reporting system.
- Created scripts that combine multiple external services to offer new features
- Trained and led an offshore team that continuously contribute to multiple projects.
- Created and maintained an CI/CD pipeline to simplify and expedite the deployment of a new start project by using CircleCI.
- Involved in development of SDK for Ads delivering located on iOS/Android.
- Trained a new member from Vietnam.

2016-04 -2018-03

Software Engineer

Works Applications Co., Ltd., Tokyo

- Involved in designing and developing the features of CRE web system based on Javascript and Java(MVC).
- Involved in system migration among AWS cloud and on-premises.
- Implemented performance improvement of the continuous integration(CI).



Education

2013-04 -2016-03

Master of Science: Computer Science

Hiroshima University - Japan

 Conducted research on system reliability with the mathematical(probabilistic) models.

2008-09 -2012-06

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science

Hebei University Of Economics And Business - China

Majored in CS and self-taught in Japanese to achieve N1 certification.



Certifications



Phone

+81 90 9982 1096

E-mail

lunaofscarlet@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/qi-luo-1302b112a/



